



# Safa Uludoğan

Nationality: Turkish Date of birth: 08/07/1995

Capacita Phone number: (+90) 5520018569 ■ Email address: safauludgn@gmail.com

in LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/safauludogan/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/safauludogan/</a>

Github: <a href="https://github.com/safauludogan">https://github.com/safauludogan</a>
Home: Ankara Elvankent, Ankara (Türkiye)

#### **ABOUT ME**

Hi, I'm Safa. I'm a Mobile App Developer with a background in Android development.

I've been working on software projects since 2010, mainly using .NET technologies. For the past six years, I've been focusing on mobile app development and have created many apps using Android Studio (Java) and Flutter. I also develop the backends for my mobile projects using .NET Core. You can find more details about my projects in the projects section.

I'm looking for a job where I can grow, learn, and be part of exciting projects.

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

# **Computer Engineering**

**Erciyes University** [ 24/09/2018 - 10/07/2023 ]

City: Kayseri | Country: Türkiye | Website: https://bm.erciyes.edu.tr/

## **Computer Programming**

**Selçuk University** [ 08/09/2015 – 07/07/2017 ]

City: Konya | Country: Türkiye | Website: <a href="https://www.selcuk.edu.tr/Birim/doganhisar\_myo">https://www.selcuk.edu.tr/Birim/doganhisar\_myo</a>

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Mobile developer

**Kamutech Yazılım** [ 25/07/2022 – 29/12/2023 ]

City: Ankara | Country: Türkiye

I previously worked as a Mobile Developer at Kamutech Yazılım. During my time there, I developed applications using Flutter and published them on both iOS and Android platforms. I was responsible for configuring store settings, performing ASO (App Store Optimization), and publishing the apps.

Some of the applications I worked on include **Bordro Takibi** and **KVKK SMS Application**. I also ensured the apps were regularly updated based on user feedback to improve their functionality and user experience.

App link: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.kamutech.kt\_iscibordo\_demo&hl=tr

## **Software developer**

*Vibe Bilişim* [ 01/02/2024 - 01/09/2024 ]

City: İstanbul | Country: Türkiye

I previously worked at **Vibe Bilişim** as both a Mobile Developer and Backend Developer. During my time there, I developed mobile applications using Flutter and created integration services using **.NET Core Windows Services**. One of my key responsibilities was building data transfer services to facilitate communication between different servers. These services, developed for companies such as **Acun Medya**, **Ferre**, **Deka**, and **Bluemint**, were used to transfer data to **Idenfit**.

I also managed the development, deployment, and optimization of mobile applications, ensuring they were user-friendly and met client needs.

## Software developer

**Targon Yazılım** [ 12/09/2024 – Current ]

City: Ankara | Country: Türkiye

I am currently working at **Targon Yazılım** as a Co-Founder. In this role, I am responsible for both the management of the company and active involvement in product development.

My primary focus is on developing mobile applications and their backend systems. I design and implement seamless, high-performance backend services while also building user-friendly mobile apps that meet client requirements. Additionally, I oversee project lifecycles, ensuring timely delivery and maintaining high-quality standards in all our products.

## **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Turkish

Other language(s):

## **English**

LISTENING A2 READING B1 WRITING B1

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION A1 SPOKEN INTERACTION A1** 

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

#### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Social Media / Flutter Dart / Android Development (Kotlin, Java) / GitHub / Gitlab Firebase / Object-Oriented Programming / Databases used: SQL, MySQL, Firebase Realtime Database / .NET / .NET Core / Windows Server NT to 2010 R2 / Web Services (IIS Apache NGINX)

## **PROJECTS**

[ 05/02/2021 - 05/08/2021 ]

#### **Calorie Counter**

In this application, I developed Kalori Counter with Android Studio(Java) and I used all Jetpack components while I've developing this app such as Room, Firebase, Dependency Injection and Navigation. Also, My project include MVVM design pattern. As of today, my app has reached 20,000 downloads. I'm still developing and fixing my project with feedback from users.

Link: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qor6dlPp618">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qor6dlPp618</a>

[ 04/01/2021 - 01/02/2021 ]

# **Agro OSC**

I made this project as a freelancer. It belongs to a company that does farming work in Uzbekistan. This project is to assign tasks and push notifications to farm workers.

Link: <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.osc.agrooscclient">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.osc.agrooscclient</a>

[10/08/2021 - 20/08/2021]

## **Baby Sleeping Sounds**

This application I made as a freelancer. It contains baby sleeping sounds. I made this app because of learning and experiencing the Google Play platform. In-app advertising strategies and app publishing that I have made and published to see the procedures is the first application.

## [26/07/2022 - 01/11/2022]

## İşçi e-Bordro

In this application, I developed İşçi e-Bordro. In this application I used many powerful libraries from pub.dev. For storage: Hive and SharedPreferences. For State Management: mobx and bloc. For network layer; dio and vexana. For graphics I used the syncfusion library. It is provided with the API provided in the application. I managed this incoming data using network layers and coded the interfaces. As of today, my app has reached 200,000 downloads. App is currently live on both iOS and Android platforms.

**Links:** https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.kamutech.kt\_iscibordo\_demo&hl=tr&gl=US | https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/i-sci-e-bordro/id1397247073?l=tr

[ 05/11/2022 – Current ]

## **Kvkk Sms**

In this application, I use exactly the same technologies that İşçi e-bordro. I use the common architecture that I have created for myself and apply it to the projects I develop. This application is generally written for transmitting documents related to KVKK to users via sms and getting them approved. The development of the application is still ongoing.